Guide to the Tony Judt Papers MC 233
New York University Archives
Tony Judt Papers
Bulk, 1995-2008
1976-2010
MC 233
New York University Archives
27.0 linear feet
The Tony Judt Papers contains research, notes, correspondence, and other material related his work as a professor and essayist. The collection spans the start of his teaching career in 1976, to his death in 2010, with heavy focus on the 1990s and 2000s.
(26 Paige boxes, 1 manuscript box, 2 index card file boxes, 1 flat box)
Judt, Tony, 1948-2010
Arrangement
This collection is separated into 10 series, loosely arranged by Judt's type of work. Several series are further divided because of the manner in which the material was originally filed or because of their breadth. See series and subseries notes for further explication.
Arrangement
Books
Articles/Essays
Subject Files
Teaching Files
Lectures/Conferences/Addresses
Administrative Files
Correspondence
Press, Interviews
Multimedia
Bibliography File
Biographical Note
Tony Robert Judt was a historian, essayist and public intellectual. He established the Remarque Institute at New York University and served as its first director. He taught at NYU from 1987 until his death from amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS) in 2010. Judt focused on French intellectual and 20th century European affairs in his teaching and writing, both academic and popular. He is perhaps best known for his 800-plus page history of Europe, Postwar.
Judt was born in London in 1948 to a middle class secular Jewish family with Eastern European roots. He spent his later teen years in Israel, volunteering as an interpreter during the Six-Day War. Judt later became disillusioned by the Zionist movement and left-wing politics. Later, he often wrote about this ideological change in the context of his identification with social democracy.
After Israel, Judt returned to Europe to study and received degrees in history from the University of Cambridge as well as École Normale Supérieure in Paris. He taught at Cambridge, University of California, Davis, University of California, Berkeley, and University of Oxford before coming to NYU. For a time in the 1980s, Judt lived in Prague and Vienna where he witnessed the political transformations of the time and became more focused on Eastern Europe in his studies and teaching.
Judt began his tenure at NYU as a professor in the Department of History. He taught at the Institute of French Studies as well, briefly serving as director in 1989. He also chaired the Department of History (1992-1993) and served as Dean for the Humanities, Faculty of Arts and Science (1993-1995). In 2006, Judt was given the title University Professor, “a rank conferred upon outstanding NYU faculty whose scholarship extends across traditional disciplinary boundaries and who are internationally recognized scholars and teachers.”
In 1992, Judt was appointed to the Erich Maria Remarque Chair in European Studies and helped establish the Remarque Institute three years later. The Institute’s purpose is to “support and promote the study of Europe and to encourage and facilitate communication between Americans and Europeans.” Remarque’s widow, Paulette Goddard, bequeathed funding for the creation of the Institute. Remarque offers fellowships and hosts programs, lectures, seminars and other events.
Judt authored and edited numerous books, 13 of which are represented in this collection. His work in French socialism and intellectual history is reflected in his earlier books including Socialism in Provence (1979), Marxism and the French Left (1979), Past Imperfect: French Intellectuals, 1944-1956 (1992), and Burden of Responsibility: Blum, Camus, Aron, and the French Twentieth Century (1998).
Throughout his career at NYU, Judt wrote prolifically for outlets such as The New York Review of Books, The New York Times and The National Review, often tying current events to history. He weighed in heavily on the September 11 terrorist attacks, war in Iraq, and matters in American and European policy. He wrote for academic journals, as well. In 2008, Foreign Policy magazine named him one of the top 100 public intellectuals. Judt won the George Orwell Special Prize for Lifetime Achievement in 2009.
Considered a public intellectual by many, Judt always said he thought of himself as a teacher first. In 2003, he was criticized for his New York Review of Books article entitled “Israel: The Alternative,” in which he described the country as an “anachronism” and proposed a bi-national one-state solution. In 2006, two lectures he was set to give on the topic were canceled due to complaints from Jewish groups over his stance on Israel. A public discussion in the press followed.
Postwar, published in 2005, was the culmination of more than a decade of research and thought. It was Judt’s last work of original historical research that he was able to physically complete himself, due to his illness. In 2008, he published a collection of essays that had mostly appeared in New York Review of Books entitled Reappraisals: Reflections on the Forgotten Twentieth Century. Later that year, he was diagnosed with ALS, but continued writing with the help of assistants to transcribe. He wrote about his illness and turned more toward autobiographical essay writing in the final years of his life, dictating many articles.
In October 2009, bound to a wheelchair and connected to a breathing apparatus, Judt delivered the annual Remarque Institute Lecture, his last public lecture, to an audience at NYU. He delivered it from memory. The lecture, entitled “What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy” was turned into the book Ill Fares the Land. Another book of Judt’s previously published essays, The Memory Chalet, was published in 2010. It contains a mix of personal and historical essays. The final book of Judt's writing, Thinking the Twentieth Century, was adapted from Judt’s conversations with colleague Timothy Snyder about his life, intellectual journey, and work just prior to his death. It was published posthumously in 2012.
Judt died August 6, 2010. He had two children with wife Jennifer Homans—Daniel and Nicholas.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains research, notes, correspondence, and other material related to Tony Judt's work as a professor, essayist and historian. The collection spans the start of his career in 1976, to his death in 2010, with heavy focus on the 1990s and 2000s.
Nearly half of the collection consists of research material and notes for Judt's books, namely Postwar. There is little material related to his personal life. Approximately one-quarter is research and notes for articles published in periodicals such as The New York Review of Books and Times Literary Supplement. The correspondence in the collection mostly comes from readers and colleagues, often commenting on his work.
Judt's teaching files are also represented and contain syllabi, reading lists and lecture notes. There are also administrative files from Judt's tenure as director of the Remarque Institute, but those are subject to a 20-year restriction period.
See notes at the series level for additional details.
Conditions Governing Access
The collection is in
off-site storage
Custodial History
The material in this collection originated from Judt's office at the Remarque Institute and his home. A significant portion was appraised and inventoried by a private party in 2011. The collection arrived at the University Archives in 2013.
Anti-defamation League.; Arendt, Hannah, 1906-1975; Aron, Raymond, 1905-1983; Blum, Léon, 1872-1950; Camus, Albert, 1913-1960; Davies, Norman; Judt, Tony, 1948-2010; New York Institute for the Humanities.; New York University. Remarque Institute.; Sartre, Jean-Paul, 1905-1980; Snyder, Timothy; Administrative records.; Anti-Americanism; Antisemitism |z United States; Arab-Israeli conflict; Articles.; bibliographies; Cold War; Correspondence.; criticism.; Dissertations.; Drafts (documents).; Essays.; Europe |x History |y 1945-; Europe |x Intellectual life |y 20th century; Europe |x Study and teaching; France |x Intellectual life |y 19th century; France |x Intellectual life |y 20th century; Iraq War, 2003-2011; Lecture notes.; Marxism |x History; Reprints.; Research notes.; Reviews (document genre); résumés (personnel records).; Social democracy; Syllabi.; transcripts.; United States |x Foreign relations |z Israel
- Series I: Books
  Arrangement
  The material in this series is organized by the title to which it relates, and then typically chronologically within each subseries.
  Subseries A: La Reconstruction du Parti Socialiste (1976)
  Subseries B: Socialism in Provence, 1871-1914 (1979)
  Subseries C: Marxism and the French Left (1986)
  Subseries D: Resistance and Revolution in Mediterranean Europe, 1939-1948 (1989)
  Subseries E: Past imperfect: French intellectuals, 1944-1956 (1992)
  Subseries F: A Grand Illusion? An Essay on Europe (1996)
  Subseries G: Burden of Responsibility (1998)
  Subseries H: The Politics of Retribution in Europe: World War II and Its Aftermath (2000)
  Subseries I: Postwar (2005)
  Subseries J: Reappraisals (2008)
  Subseries K: Thinking the Twentieth Century (2012)
  Subseries L: Ill Fares the Land (2010)
  Subseries M: The Memory Chalet (2010)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains notes, research, drafts and reviews related to the books Judt authored throughout his career.
  The bulk of the material in this series is from Postwar. There are also notes and research related to Past Imperfect, A Grand Illusion?, and Burden of Responsibility. Judt's papers contained drafts of essay collections he titled "Israel Book," "State of Exception" and "Essays." All of these appear to be alternative titles for Reappraisals.
  The subseries also contain reviews and correspondence related to each of Judt's works. Correspondence from readers can also be found in Series VII: Correspondence.
  - Subseries A: La Reconstruction du Parti Socialiste (1976)
    - Review, circa 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Subseries B: Socialism in Provence, 1871-1914 (1979)
    - Reviews, circa 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Subseries C: Marxism and the French Left (1986)
    - Reviews, circa 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Reviews, circa 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Reviews, circa 1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Subseries D: Resistance and Revolution in Mediterranean Europe, 1939-1948 (1989)
    - Reviews, circa 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Subseries E: Past imperfect: French intellectuals, 1944-1956 (1992)
    - Main notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Main notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Main notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Main notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Main notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Main notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Main notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Main notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Source notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Source notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Source notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Source notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Source notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Source notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - French intellectuals in 20th c. notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Dates (unsorted) - notes, correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Fr. intellectuals 1944-1956 notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Fr. intellectuals 1944-1956 notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Fr. intellectuals 1944-1956 notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Fr. intellectuals 1944-1956 notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Fellow travs. and anti-Am. notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Fr. intells. pre-1944 notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Fr. intells. pre-1944 notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Fr. intells. pre-1944 notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - France: trials and related notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Fr. intells. 1956- notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Fr. intells and Communism notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - E. European intells. all notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Italian thought notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - General European intellectual notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - USSR and Moscow trials notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Italian Intellectuals notes (empty), undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - General E. European History notes (empty), undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - E. European History 1944-1956 notes (empty), undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - E. Europe: Trials notes (empty), undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - French Politics post-1944 notes (empty), undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - General notes and quotes, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Jacket art, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Reviews, press, letters, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Reviews, press, letters, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Reviews, press, letters, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Reviews, press, letters, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Reviews, press, letters, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Reviews, press, letters, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Reviews, press, letters, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Reviews, press, letters, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Reviews, press, letters, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Misc., 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Subseries F: A Grand Illusion? An Essay on Europe (1996)
    - draft, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - draft, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - draft, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - draft, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - reviews, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - reviews, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - reviews, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Subseries G: Burden of Responsibility (1998)
    - contractual letter, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Aron notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Aron notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Aron notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Aron notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Aron notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Aron research, undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Aron research, undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Aron research, undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Aron draft, undated (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Aron draft, undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Camus notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Camus notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Camus notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Camus notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Camus draft, undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Camus draft, undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Camus draft, undated (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Blum notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Blum notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Blum notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Blum notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - research, draft, undated (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - reviews, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - reviews, correspondence, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - reviews, correspondence, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - reviews, correspondence, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - reviews, correspondence, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - reviews, correspondence, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - reviews, correspondence, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - reviews, correspondence, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Subseries H: The Politics of Retribution in Europe: World War II and Its Aftermath (2000)
    - review, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Corbis, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Subseries I: Postwar (2005)
    This subseries is further divided to reflect Judt's writing process. His research and notes from Postwar appear in the collection in several groupings that were brought together during processing. These include sets of notes organized by an outline system, as well as by chapter and subject. The way Judt organized his notes is not necessarily reflected in the published version of the book.
    Sub-subseries i: Outline Notes
    Sub-subseries ii: Subject Notes
    Sub-subseries iii: Chapter Notes
    Sub-subseries iv: Other Notes and Drafts
    Sub-subseries v: Master Set 1st Madeup - Author's Galleys
    Sub-subseries vi: Author's correx to final pass
    Sub-subseries vii: "Setting MS" manuscript
    Sub-subseries viii: Press, reviews, correspondence
    - Sub-subseries i: Outline Notes, undated
      - 1A: Economic Consequences of War, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - 1B: Human Consequences of War, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - 1C: Refugees/Pop Movts/Frontiers, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - 1C: Refugees/Pop Movts/Frontiers, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - 1D: Civil Wars, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - 1E: Psychological Legacy, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - 1F: Trials and Purges, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - 1F: Trials and Purges, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - 1G: Popular Justice/Revenge, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - 1H: Denazification and Outcomes, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - 1J: Amnesias - 'Stunde Nul' [sic], undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - 1X: Neutrals in WW2, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - 2A: Resistance Illusions, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - 2B: Varieties of War Destruction, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - 2C: Plans and Planning, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - 2D: Marshall Plan, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - 2D: Marshall Plan, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - 2DD: Prelude to Marshall Plan, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - 2DD: Prelude to Marshall Plan, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - 2E: EPA/ECSC, etc., undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - 2E: EPA/ECSC, etc., undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - 2F: Industrialisation in East (empty), undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - 2G: Urban Rebuilding (empty), undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - 2H: Welfare State, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - 2J: Pol. reforms and innovations, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - 2K: GB '45-'51, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - 2K: GB '45-'51, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - 2L: Daily life in post-war Europe (empty), undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - 2X: [Bretton Woods], undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - 3A: Wartime Origins of Cold War, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - 3B: American Expectations, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - 3C: British Expectations, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - 3D: French Motives, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - 3E: Soviet Objectives, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - 3E: Soviet Objectives, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - 3F: Partition of Germany, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - 3F: Partition of Germany, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - 3G: Truman Doctrine, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - 3H: Slicing the Salami, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - 3H: Slicing the Salami, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - 3J: Cominform/Yugoslavia, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - 3J: Cominform/Yugoslavia, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - 3K: Berlin, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - 3L: NATO, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - 3M: Korea, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - 3X: (untitled), undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - 4A: Poland (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - 4C: East European economies - 'not needed' (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - 4E: Anti-Semitism-Nationalism, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - 4E: Anti-Semitism-Nationalism, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - 4E: Anti-Semitism-Nationalism, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - 4E: Anti-Semitism-Nationalism, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - 5A: Generation of 1945 (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - 5B: Intellectuals in France (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - 5C: Intellectuals in GB (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - 5D: Intellectuals in West Europe (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - 5E: Intellectuals in East Europe (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - 5F: Anti-Fascism, Progressivism (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - 5G: Cultural Cold War (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - 5H: Cinema (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - 5J: Religion, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - 5J: Religion, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - 5J: Religion, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - 5J: Religion, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - 5K: Mass Movements (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - 6A: International 1953-1963, undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
      - 6A: International 1953-1963, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - 6A: International 1953-1963, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - 6A: International 1953-1963, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - 6B: Great Britain (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - 6C: Germany (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - 6D: France (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - 6E: Italy (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - 6F: Austria (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - 6G: USSR (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - 6H: Warsaw Pact & Comecon (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - 6J: Other (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - 6K: ECSC-EEC (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - 6L: EDC (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - 6M: EFTA (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
      - 7A: Decolonisation (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
      - 7B: Suez & After, undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
      - 7B: Suez & After, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
      - 7C: Algeria (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
      - 7D: Inward Migration (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
      - 7E: Post-Stalinism to 1956 (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
      - 7F: Hungary (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
      - 7G: Disillusion & Depoliticisation, undated (Box 3, Folder 51)
      - 7G: Disillusion & Depoliticisation, undated (Box 3, Folder 52)
      - 7G: Disillusion & Depoliticisation, undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
      - 8A: Production, undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
      - 8A: Production, undated (Box 3, Folder 55)
      - 8B: Babies, Migrants, undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
      - 8C: Labour & Employment, undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
      - 8D: Consumption, undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
      - 8E: Health, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - 8F: Tourism, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - 8G: Entertainment & Media, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - 8H: Transportation, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - 8J: GB Case, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - 8K: German Case, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - 8L: Americanisation?, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - 8X: Urbanisation, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - 9A: Social Democracy and Labour, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - 9B: Welfare reforms (empty), undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - 9C: Austro-Scandinavian model, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - 9D: Moral Reforms, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - 9E: Reform Communism, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - 9F: Kruschev era in USSR, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - 9G: European Ideas (empty), undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - 9H: European Fashions, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - 9J: European Arts, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - 9K: Apotheosis of State (1A-->1F), undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - 10A: Education & Youth, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - 10B: Academic Ideas and Disciplines, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - 10C: Hitler's Children & Gen. Gap (empty), undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - 10D: Music, style, sex, cinema, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - 10E: 1968-1971: France, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - 10F: 1968-1971: Germany, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - 10G: 1968-1971: Italy, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - 10H: 1968-1970: Poland, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - 10J: 1968-1969: Czechoslovakia, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - 10K: International Political Context, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - 10L: International ideol. context, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - 10M: Economic Context (empty), undated (Box 4, Folder 30)